* English
    
      English Korean

### PRIVACY POLICY

Welcome to Yostar, the website and online service of Yostar, Inc. (collectively,“Yostar”, “we” or “us”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how information about you or associated with you (collectively, “personal information”) is collected, used and disclosed by Yostar, Inc, and its affiliates, which own and operate Yostar.

This Privacy Policy applies to our websites, including https://Yo-star.com and [https://yostar.co.jp/](https://yostar.co.jp/) , and our mobile apps for iPhone, Android and Windows mobile devices (collectively, “our Service”). By accessing or using our Service, you hereby signify that you have read, understood and agree to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### 1\. Information which we’ll collect and use

Generally. We will only process your personal information in accordance with applicable information protection and privacy laws. We collect personal information from you, our users, in order to provide you with a personalized, useful, and efficient experience. If you’ve created a profile and/or registered with our Service, you’ll be asked to agree to provide this information in order to access our Service. This consent provides us with the legal basis we require under applicable law(s) to process your personal information. You maintain the right to withdraw such consent at any time. If you do not agree to our use of your personal information in line with this Policy, please do not use our Service.

The categories of information we collect can include:

Information you provide. You may use the Service without providing any personal information, but you must register and create a profile to participate in our official forums. We may collect and store personal information or you will voluntarily provide to us in some manner or another your name, email address, user name and password when you register for our Service. We may also collect any communications between you and Yostar, as well as any information you provide if you take part in any interactive features of our Service. Information that is part of your profile will be viewable to the public and to other members of our Service.

Information collected through the use of our Service. After you’ve set up your account, you may choose to provide additional information which may be shared through public profiles. Such information can be your photograph or avatar, biographical content, and other information (collectively, “Profile Information”). You control how much personal identifying information you wish to disclose to the public profile. We also collect information about how you use our Service and about your actions on our Service. This may include your Service usage and activities, gaming levels, interactions with others on our Service and user content you post on our Service, as well as other content (collectively, “User Content”). Please remember that Yostar may, but has no obligation to, monitor User Content posted by our users.

Information we receive from third party sites. When you interact with our site through various third-party channels, we may receive information from these channels. Third-party channels being: Facebook, Google+, Twitter, and other social media platforms. The information we may receive includes your: profile information, profile picture, gender, user name, user ID associated with your social media account, age range, language, country, friends list, and any other information you permit the social network to share with third parties. We may use your friend and/or friends’ data to let you know what he/she/they are doing on our Service; and similarly, let your friend and/or friends know what you are doing on our Service. The data we receive is dependent upon your privacy settings with the social network(s). We will not post information about you on third party social media sites without your consent. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to our website or to our Service.

Address Book Information. With your permission, Yostar may access your contact list available on your mobile device or in your email accounts. We may locate your friends and contacts via your contact list in order to invite your friends and contacts to connect with our Service. When we invite your friends to join our Service, we will include your name and photo to let them know that you are the person extending the invitation. After sending these invitations, we may also send reminder emails to your invitees on your behalf. We will store these contacts for the purpose of alerting you when your contacts join Yostar at a later time so that you may connect with them on our Service; and to further suggest friends and connections to other members of Yostar.

We’ll use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of our Service, as well as to communicate directly with you, such as to send you email messages and push notifications, and permit you to communicate with others on our Service or on social media or invite others to join our Service. We may combine information internally across different Service offerings or games to enhance your experience with our Service. For example, we may identify a friend you may know from one service so as to suggest that you may engage with that friend on another service. We may let your friends on one service know about your activities on another service. For example, we may send an email to your friend(s) on one of our Games to let them know that you're active on our Games, and we may include your profile picture in the email so that your friend(s) will recognize you. We may also use information about your activities on our Service to provide personalized content, including targeted content and advertising. We may also send you Service-related emails or messages (e.g., account verification, account status, change or updates to features of our Service, technical and security notifications). For more information about your communication preferences, see “Your Choices Regarding Your Information” down below.

Use of cookies and other technology to collect information. We and our third-party business partners will automatically collect certain types of usage information when you visit our website or use our Service. When you visit our Service, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use our Service (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click, how frequently you access the Service, and other actions you take on our Service). This will allow us to track your usage of the Service over time. We may collect log file information from your browser or mobile device each time you access our Service. Log file information may include anonymous information, such as your: web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, information about your mobile device, referring/exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on our Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information(s). We may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to anonymously track the online usage patterns of our users. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by the recipients. The information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of our Service. We may also collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for our Service and to understand more about the demographics of our users. These tools collect information sent by your browser or mobile device(s). Information collected includes the pages you’ve visited, your use of third-party applications, and other information that’ll assists us in analyzing and improving our Service. Although we do our best to honor the privacy preferences of our visitors, we are not able to respond to Do Not Track signals from your browser at this time.

When you access our Service by or through a mobile device, we may receive or collect and store a unique set of identification numbers associated with your device or your mobile application. This may include, for example: a unique device ID, Unique ID for Advertisers (“IDFA”), Google Ad ID, or Windows Advertising ID, MAC address, mobile carrier, device type, model and manufacturer, mobile device operating system brand and model, phone number; all of which, are dependent of your mobile device settings. In addition, we create a unique user ID to track your use of our Service. This unique user ID helps us to track the games you’re playing.

We use or may use the information collected through cookies, log file, device identifiers, location data and clear gifs information to:

* (a) Remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site;
* (b) Provide custom, personalized content and information, including targeted content and advertisement;
* (c) Provide and monitor the effectiveness of our Service;
* (d) Monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, usage, and demographic patterns on our website and our Service;
* (e) Diagnose or fix technology and/or technical problems;
* (f) Otherwise to plan for and enhance our Service.

### 2\. Sharing Information

We may share your personal information in the following instances described below, not beyond the reasonable purpose of our Service and not in anyway to sell or disclose your personal information for profit. For further information on your choices regarding your information, refer to the “Your Choices Regarding Your Information” section below.l

We may also share your personal information with:

* (a). Third-parties with your permission. For example, you may have the option to share your activities on Yostar with your friends through email, text or on various social media sites;
* (b). Other brands owned or controlled by Yostar and other companies owned by or under common ownership as Yostar. This may also include our subsidiaries (i.e., any organization we own or control) or our head holding company (i.e., any organization that owns or controls us) and any subsidiaries it owns. These companies will use your personal information in the same way as we can under this Policy;
* (c). Other parties whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you;
* (d). Third-party vendors, consultants and other service providers that perform services on our behalf, in order to carry out their work for us, which may include identifying and serving targeted advertisements, content or service fulfillment, or providing analytics services;
* (e). Other parties in connection with any company transaction, such as a merger, sale of all or a portion of company assets or shares, re-organization, financing, change of control or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company or third-party or in the event of bankruptcy and/or related similar proceedings;
* (f). Third-parties as required to: (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, subpoena and/or court order, legal process or other government request; (ii) enforce our Terms of Use Agreement, including the investigation of potential violations thereof; (iii) investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations; (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or the safety of Yostar, its users or the public as required or permitted by law(s) and; (v) detect, prevent or otherwise address criminal (including fraud or stalking), security or technical issues.

We may also share information with others in an aggregated and anonymous form that does not reasonably identify you directly as an individual.

### 3\. Your Choices Regarding Your Information Profile and Data Sharing Settings. You may change some of your data sharing preferences in the Settings page.

Push Notifications. We may occasionally send you push notifications through our mobile applications to send you game updates, high scores and other service related notifications that may be of importance to you. You may at any time opt-out from receiving these types of communications by turning them off at the device level through your settings.l

Marketing Communications. If you do not wish to receive promotional emails, you can click the "unsubscribe" button on promotional email communications. Note that you are not permitted to unsubscribe or opt-out of non-promotional messages regarding your account, such as account verification, change or updates to features of our Service, or technical and security notices.

Online Advertising. We may permit third-party online advertising networks, social media companies, and other parties to collect information about your use of our website and apps over time so that they may play or display ads that may be relevant to your interests on our Service as well as on other websites or apps. Typically, the information we share is provided through cookies or similar tracking technologies. The only way to completely “opt out” of the collection of any information through cookies or other tracking technology is to actively manage the settings on your browser or mobile device. Please refer to your browser’s or mobile device’s technical information for instructions on how to delete or disable cookies and/or other tracking/recording tools. (To learn more about cookies, clear gifs/web beacons and related technologies, you may wish to visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and/or the Network Advertising Initiative's online resources, at [https://www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/) ). If you access our service on your mobile device, you may not be able to control tracking technologies through settings.

Data Retention: We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you our Service. Please contact us at [info@Yo-star.com](mailto:info@Yo-star.com) if you wish to permanently delete your account from our systems. Please be aware that we will not be able to delete any content you have shared with others or with social media sites.

Deleting or Anonymizing Your Content: If you are under 18 years of age, you may request that the User Content which you posted to our Service to be deleted or anonymized such that your personal information will not be identifiable publicly on our Service. You can request to do so by contacting us at [info@Yo-star.com](mailto:info@Yo-star.com) While we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to delete or anonymize your User Content upon request, please be aware that due to the social nature of our Service, you may not be able to completely remove all of your personal identifiable User Content if, for example, said content has been stored, republished, or reposted by another user or other third-party entities. We may also maintain your information in identifiable form for our internal use, even if your personal information is no longer visible to the public on our Service.

### 4\. Security And Storage of Information

Yostar cares about the security of your information. As such, we’ll use commercially reasonable physical, administrative, and technological safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information which we collect and that we share with our service providers. However, no security system is impenetrable and we cannot guarantee 100% the security of our systems. In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation; and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable law(s) and regulation(s).

Your information collected through our Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Yostar or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain its facilities. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and observes law(s) and/or policies that may differ from the U.S., please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as the jurisdiction of the U.S.; and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or any other country in which Company or its parent, subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.

### 5\. Individuals Under the Age of 13

Our Service and its content are not directed at children under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we’ve collected personal information from a minor under the age of 13 without parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information collected from a minor under the age of 13, please contact us at [info@Yo-star.com](mailto:info@Yo-star.com).

### 6\. Sensitive Personal Information

Subject to the following paragraph, we ask that you do not send us, and do not disclose, any of the following sensitive personal information , including without limitation to your social security number, information related to personal property, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometrics or genetic characteristics, criminal background or trade union membership, on or through our Forums, Social Media, Service or otherwise.

If you send or disclose any sensitive personal data to us when you submit user generated content to our Forums, Social Media or Service, then you consent to our processing and use of such sensitive personal information in accordance with this Policy. If you do not consent to our processing and use of such sensitive personal information, then you must not submit to us such user generated content to our Forums, Social Media, and Service or otherwise. Where you suffer any loss, damage or otherwise due to such unpermitted disclosure to us, you shall undertake all liabilities therefrom.

### 7\. Complaints

We are committed to resolving any complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. If you would like to make a complaint regarding this Policy or our practices in relation to your personal information, please contact us at: [info@Yo-star.com](mailto: info@Yo-star.com) . We will reply to your complaint as soon as we can or within 45 days. We hope to resolve any complaint brought to our attention, however if you feel that your complaint has not been adequately resolved, you reserve the right to contact your local data protection supervisory authority; which for the UK, is the Information Commissioner’s Office.

### 8\. EU - U.S. Privacy Shield

Yostar complies with the EU - U.S. Privacy Shield Framework set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data transferred from the EU to the United States. We’re certified by the Department of Commerce that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall take precedence. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, the Privacy Shield Principles and to view our certification, please visit [www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome).

As described in this Privacy Policy, Yostar is accountable for personal information which it receives and subsequently transfers to third-parties. If third-parties who process personal information on our behalf do so in a manner that does not comply with the Privacy Shield Principles, we are accountable for their non-compliance, unless proven that we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Yostar is committed to resolving complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this Policy should first contact us at: [info@Yo-star.com](mailto: info@Yo-star.com).

Yostar is further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to Jams, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not resolved your complaint, please visit [https://jamsadr.com](https://jamsadr.com/) for more information or to file a complaint. The services of Jams are provided at no cost to you.

Yostar is further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. Mediations will be conducted pursuant to JAMS International Mediation Rules unless the parties have specified a different set of Rules or Procedures. Download the JAMS International Mediation Rules, [here](https://www.jamsadr.com/international-mediation-rules/) . If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not resolved your complaint, please visit [https://jamsadr.com](https://jamsadr.com/) for more information or to file a complaint. The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you.

### 9\. Links to Third Party Websites

The Service may contain links to and from third party websites of our business partners, advertisers, social media sites, and our users may post links to third party websites. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies. Please check their own policies before you submit any information to our affiliated third-party websites.

### 10\. Updates to This Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Policy moving forward. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the "Last Revision" date below and will post the updated Policy on this page. If you object to any changes, you may close your account. Continuing to use our Service after we publish changes to this Privacy Policy means that you are consenting to the changes.

### 11\. Contacting Us

If you have questions about this Policy, please contact us at [https://jamsadr.com](https://jamsadr.com/) or write to us at: YOSTAR (HONG KONG) LIMITED.

Address: Room 06,13A/ F.,South Tower,World Finance Centre,Harbour City,17 Canton Road,Tsim Sha Tsui,Kowloon,Hong Kong

### 12\. Last Revision Date

This Policy was last revised on, and effective as of April 9th, 2019.
